{
  "participantID": "9a2babc2-6163-4586-aca8-3f841784458a",
  "demographicsAnswers": [
    {
      "participantID": "9a2babc2-6163-4586-aca8-3f841784458a",
      "age": 22,
      "gender": "female",
      "experience": "bachelor-inf",
      "englishLevel": "mother-tongue"
    }
  ],
  "score": 8,
  "questionData": {
    "question0": {
      "questionIndex": 0,
      "questionOrder": 1,
      "questionText": "jump left",
      "caseFormat": "kebab1",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "jump-lelt",
        "junmp-left",
        "jump-left",
        "junp-left"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
      "selectedOption": "jump-left",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": 36030.29999999702
    },
    "question1": {
      "questionIndex": 1,
      "questionOrder": 2,
      "questionText": "query indexes",
      "caseFormat": "camel3",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "queryIndexes",
        "querryIndexes",
        "quaryIndexes",
        "queryInbexes"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
      "selectedOption": "queryIndexes",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": 1059.7000000029802
    },
    "question2": {
      "questionIndex": 2,
      "questionOrder": 3,
      "questionText": "algorithm numbers",
      "caseFormat": "kebab2",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "algortithm-numbers",
        "algorithm-nunbers",
        "algorithmn-numbers",
        "algorithm-numbers"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
      "selectedOption": "algorithm-numbers",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "timeTaken": 1892.7999999970198
    },
    "question3": {
      "questionIndex": 3,
      "questionOrder": 4,
      "questionText": "wording change",
      "caseFormat": "camel4",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "wordingChange",
        "wordingChane",
        "wardingChange",
        "wordingChagne"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
      "selectedOption": "wordingChange",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": 2697.5
    },
    "question4": {
      "questionIndex": 4,
      "questionOrder": 5,
      "questionText": "algorithm numbers",
      "caseFormat": "camel2",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "algorithmNunbers",
        "algortithmNumbers",
        "algorithmnNumbers",
        "algorithmNumbers"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
      "selectedOption": "algorithmNumbers",
      "isCorrect": false,
      "timeTaken": 3550.2000000029802
    },
    "question5": {
      "questionIndex": 5,
      "questionOrder": 6,
      "questionText": "query indexes",
      "caseFormat": "kebab3",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "querry-indexes",
        "quary-indexes",
        "query-indexes",
        "query-inbexes"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
      "selectedOption": "query-indexes",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": 1310.8999999910593
    },
    "question6": {
      "questionIndex": 6,
      "questionOrder": 7,
      "questionText": "packet size",
      "caseFormat": "kebab5",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "packets-size",
        "packet-size",
        "packet-side",
        "paket-Size"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
      "selectedOption": "packet-size",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": 2601.6000000089407
    },
    "question7": {
      "questionIndex": 7,
      "questionOrder": 8,
      "questionText": "jump left",
      "caseFormat": "camel1",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "jumpLeft",
        "jumpLelt",
        "jumnpLeft",
        "junpLeft"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
      "selectedOption": "jumpLeft",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": 1070.7999999970198
    },
    "question8": {
      "questionIndex": 8,
      "questionOrder": 9,
      "questionText": "wording change",
      "caseFormat": "kebab4",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "wording-chagne",
        "wording-change",
        "wording-chane",
        "warding-change"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
      "selectedOption": "wording-change",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": 1716.9000000059605
    },
    "question9": {
      "questionIndex": 9,
      "questionOrder": 10,
      "questionText": "packet size",
      "caseFormat": "camel5",
      "optionsGiven": [
        "packetsSize",
        "packetSide",
        "packetSize",
        "paketSize"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
      "selectedOption": "packetSize",
      "isCorrect": true,
      "timeTaken": 1995.5999999940395
    }
  }
}
